Guide to the H. Lynn Womack papers, 1945-1994
Womack, H. Lynn papers, 1945-1994
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
H. Lynn Womack papers 1945-1994
7441
H. Lynn Womack
5 cubic feet
Correspondence, business records, newspaper clippings, court records, manuscripts, photographs, catalogues, brochures, advertisements.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The H. Lynn Womack papers include business records of the Guild Press, the Guild Book Service, the Grecian Guild, the Potomac News Company, and Village Books and Press, all of an erotic and pornographic nature. Also, correspondence with Richard Schlegel and others, gay periodicals, manuscripts of erotic and pornographic stories, and an extensive collection of pornographic mail order catalogs.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
H. Lynn Womack (1923-1985) was a headmaster of a boys' school in the 1940s and then a professor of Philosophy at George Washington University. In 1952, he bought the small company Guild Press, and as publisher, editor, and distributor, turned it into a profitable gay publishing company with numerous affilated enterprises. The United States Postal Service tried to stop the circulation of MANUAL, TRIM, and GRECIAN GUILD PICTORIAL, but he took them to court and won the case on appeal in the U.S. Supreme Court (Manual Enterprises Inc. v. J. Edward Day) in 1962. This ruling changed the definintion of obscenity and its relationship to gay pornography.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Series I. of the H. Lynn Womack papers consists of correspondence, business records, newspaper clippings, and briefs, transcripts, and records of court cases pertaining to pornography and obscenity; also, manuscripts, correspondence, and photographs pertaining to the Guild Book Service and its affiliated enterprises, including the Guild Press, Potomac News Company, Central Sales, the Grecian Guild, Village Books, Village Press, and Media Arts. Included is the correspondence of the editors of these enterprises, including Rick Sampson, Ronnie Anderson, J.J. Proferes, and Ralph Church. Additional Guild Press records from Womack's estate include correspondence between Womack and various photographers and publishers including Randolph Benson of Trim magazine, model releases and related publication papers, photographic negatives and proofs of pictures published in various Womack magazines, and transparencies of similar material. Also, seals for Potomac Associates (1958) and Howell Academy for Boys, Inc. (1945). Series II. is an extensive collection of pornographic mail order catalogues, brochures, advertisements, and other mailings.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Womack, H. Lynn, 1923-1985.; Schlegel, Richard.; Guild Press.; Guild Book Service.; Village Books and Press.; Grecian Guild.; Potomac News Company.
Subjects:
Pornography.; Erotica.; Sex oriented businesses.; Mail order businesses.; Pornography--Catalogs.; Gay men--Books and reading.; Obscenity (law).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
PROVENANCE
Gift of George Fisher.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Series I. is maintained as it arrived, in no particular order. Materials in Box 5 were added to the collection in 2009, several years after the original acquisition. Series II. is arranged in alphabetical order.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Womack and Guild Book Service Files
Boxes 1-2, 5-9
Series II. Mail Order Catalogs and Advertisements
Boxes 2-4
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Womack and Guild Book Service Files
  - Herman Lynn Womack personal papers, including newspaper clippings pertaining to his arrest on obscenity charges, and the United States District Court Grand Jury proceedings against Womack and others, 3 November 1969. (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - United States District Court Grand Jury, Official Transcript of Proceedings, 10 March 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - United States District Court Grand Jury Charge, 3 Nov 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 17 Nov 1960 legal lists (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Pornography, articles and papers (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Newspapers pertaining to Womack sentencing and arrest, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Obscenity, articles (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Obscenity legal cases, briefs (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Obscenity cases, clippings, and legal papers pertaining to Womack and Potomac News Company (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Obscenity, Supreme Court legal cases (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
  - Luros legal case (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Blount, Postmaster General vs. Rizzi, doing business as The Mail Box (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CDL Reporter (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Several obscenity legal cases, corresp9ondence, and First Amendment Lawyers Association printed material (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Guild Press author's contract (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - United States vs. Spinar and Germain (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Manual Enterprises vs. Day (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rubber Goods (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Portsmouth, Virginia; Village Books legal cases (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - North Carolina vs. Dick McCluney (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Michigan vs. MGA Theatres, Gamecock, Argo Land Company (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Hoyt vs. Minnesota; "Mix Mates" magazine (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Charlene Mitchell vs. Joseph L. Donovan (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - DSI (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - United States vs. Dellapia (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Marvin Miller (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Lee Art Theatre (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Liberty of Congress (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Nixon (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - United States vs. "Sexual Freedom" (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Trojan Book Service (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Massachusetts and Boston vs. Hunt and Palladino (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Jim Hall correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Cobra Press, Amsterdam, Holland (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Andrews Manor (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ralph Ginzburg (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Obscenity charges, Newport News, Queen and Ferraro (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 101 Book Sales (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Oliver Layton Press (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Village Books (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Book Guild of America (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Trojan Book Service (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Phallic Development in the White Male (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - One Confidential; The Treasure Chest Compendium (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Foreign Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 48-49)
  - Central Sales, Legal (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Central Sales, Catalogs (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Bob Anthony Studio (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Ben Grandy Company (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - New Market Possibilities; Richard Schlegel Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Post Office Policies (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Grecian Guild Letters and Pictures (Box 1, Folder 56-57)
  - Original typescript chapters 27-29 of a pornographic novel (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - "Pornography and Violence" by Irving Younger (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Guild Press Photo Studio correspondence (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Jay Mitchell Studio (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Rick Dion Studio, Portland Oregon (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 1968 Convention (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - International Sex Equality Anonymous, Montreal (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Photo correspondence (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Photo Studio brochures (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - General correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 67-69)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Guild Press correspondence with prospective authors (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
  - Disus; Nick Krysalka correspondence (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Ralph Chambers correspondence, Daddy's Nympho manuscript (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photographs and pieces of short prose (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Clothing catalogues (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript and typescript (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pornographic story, "The Spit and the Pendulum" (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Herb Vernon (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Clippings (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Village Books mailings and order forms (Box 2, Folder 12-14)
  - Rhodesia (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Village Books mailings and order forms (Box 2, Folder 16-18)
  - Enterprises subsequent to Village Books (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Domestic and foreign check-off lists (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Clippings (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Guild Book Service, mailings 1-14 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Guild Book Service, mailings 15-26 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Guild Book Service, mailings 27-35 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Guild Book Service, mailings 36-47 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Guild Book Service, mailings 48-58 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Guild Book Service, mailings 59-74 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Village Books and Press, mailings 1-19 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Village Books and Press, mailings 20-34 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Village Books and Press, mailings 35-45 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Mark II Theatre, mailings 1-26 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Potomac News Company (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Guild Press correspondence, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
  - Photograph submissions to Grecian Guild Pictorial, 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
  - Correspondence and submissions to Guild Books, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
  - Media Arts, mailings 1-17 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Media Arts, mailings 18-40 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Media Arts, mailings 41-64 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Photographs and negatives of nude men (Box 2, Folder 42-44)
  - Photographs and negatives of nude men (Box 5, Folder 1-51)
  - Negatives of nude men (Box 6)
  - Negatives of nude men (Box 7)
  - Negatives of nude men (Box 8)
  - Clothing and fashion brochures (Box 2, Folder 45-47)
  - International Guild Travel Guide (Box 2, Folder 48-51)
  - Miscellaneous erotic and pornographic catalogues, brochures, and mailings (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Castillo correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1994 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Trim, Randolph Benson (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Guild Press brochures (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Brochures from other publishers (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Model releases (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Embossing stamps for Potomac Associates and for Howell Academy for Boys (Box 9)
- Series II. Mail Order Catalogs and Advertisements
  - Ace Services (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Action Line (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Ace Advertising Service, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Adam's Enterprises (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Adams Forwarding Service (Dansk Exports) (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - The Adult Company (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Adult and Parents Guidance Institute (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Alameda Book Sales (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - ADC-Alan Distributing Company (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - All Star Enterprises (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - All Star Distributors (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Alpha 1 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Amazon Productions (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Bob Anthony (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Apollo (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Aquarius (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Argyle Company (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Dale Armstrong and Associates (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Artemis Books (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Artista Book Club (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Athens West (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Atol Ltd. (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Joseph W. Barnes (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Basic Health Aids (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Bayou Studios (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Bates, Adler, and Co. (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Behaviour Modification, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Bellatrix Publishing (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - BSP - Behavioural Science Press (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Bentley Co. (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Berkshire Guild (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Bertel Corp. (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Betta Health Products (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Bizarre Productions (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - BK Enterprises (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Book Art Co. (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Book Bin (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Book Bargains (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Book Mark (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Books Unlimited (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Brad-Lee Publications (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - J. Brian Enterprises (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Calafran Enterprises, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - John Amslow and Assoc. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cal-Mail (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Cameo (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Candor Productions ("The Real Thing") (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - CBI (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Central Products (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Central Sales Ltd. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Centurion Distributors, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Charisma, Movie-of-the-Month-Club (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Cienega Distributors (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Cinerotic Film Club of America (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Club Baths (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Collector's Corner (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - P. Collins (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Commander Books (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Craig (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - B. La Croix (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Crown House (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Cybertype (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - DAK Products (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - David of California (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - D.A.M.I. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Dansk Foto Colour USA (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - D G Sales (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Daisy Chain Letter (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Danish Advertising (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - David of California (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Davis Productions (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Dean's Enterprise (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Delas Art Studio (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Denmark Imports (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Alan Dexter (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Different Products Unlimited (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - DSI (Box 3, Folder 41-44)
  - Directory Services (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Diverse (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Diversified Products (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - F/S Pub., Inc. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - FSI (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Flower Direct Mail (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Fotoflair International (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Frank Williams (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - F.R.E.E. (International Correspondence Club) (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Freedom Press (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - GBP-G. B. Productions (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - G and M Enterprises (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Gary's Studios (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - GEM Productions (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - GMBH Colorfilm, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Go Go Products (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Goldenrod (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Gold Line (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Graduate Enterprises (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Grand Prix Photo Arts (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Great Western Services (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Greenbriar Club, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Greyhuff (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - GW Enterprises (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Hallmark House (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - John Harrison (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Hartman, Assoc. (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Health Aid Distributors (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Heart Studios (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Helvardsen-Kohn Opticals, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Hogarth Guild (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Hollywood Selections (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Hollywood Showcase (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - H.R.A. and Associates Homosexual Research Association (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Homophile Youth Movement - HYMN (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - House of David (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - House of Price (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - IPS - International Phallic Society, Ltd. (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Ionos Mailers (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Jay Mitchell Studios (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Jensen Ent., Mark (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Joe Miller Studio (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Kamera (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Robert Kent (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Mr. Kenneth (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Marie Kis (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - L'Affaire (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Leather Lads (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Leung's (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Leisure Mailers (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Limited Publishers Guild (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - LSI (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Lunar Sales (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Lux Publications (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Lyle Stuart, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Merlin Photographic (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Metro Books (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - M.D. Press (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - MPS Associates (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Madison Square Books (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - John Merryweather Inc. - JMI (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Magazine of Modern Sex (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Mid-City (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Male Call (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Midwest Photo Services (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Milo of Los Angeles (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Mino-Cini (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Monarch Products (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - NAA (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - National Productions (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Eddie Nelson and Associates (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Marlboro Publishing Company (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Nema (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Newbern Company (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - New York Hymnal (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Nova Arts (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Northern News/Greyhuff (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Olympia Selections (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - One, Incorporated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Mark IV Enterprises, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - M. Maurice (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Maytime Production Co. Inc. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Media Arts (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Media-Data, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Medical Press of New York (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Medical Products of New York (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Medon Dist., Ltd. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Barbara Martine (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Option Publishes Corp. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Osiris (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Overstock Book Co. Inc. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Pacifica (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Pan Graphic, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Panu-Co. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Paramount Classics (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Park-Miller Theatre (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Parkway House (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Paulchen Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Pen Pals International (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Penitentiary Publishing (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Pent-R Books, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Pen-Vib (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Peters, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Pharaoh Designs, Ltd. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Photographer's Choice (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Photographer's Guild (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Lioneer Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - La Plume (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Poses (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Potpourri (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Powell Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Premier (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Premium Productions (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Art Printz (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Private Audience Films, Co. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Private Collections, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - QQ Publ. Co. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Alan Rand (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Rand Mailers (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Randolph P.A. (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - RAS Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - The Reel Thing - Candor Productions (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Regal Book Company (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Regent House (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Rex (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Riviera Company (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Riviera Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Roberts (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - John Rodriguez (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Rogue Studios (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Roger of Hollywood (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Romans (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Rogy's (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Safe-P-Products (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - S and D Products (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Le Salon (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Scandia (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Seven Star Productions (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Sex Research Reports, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Sex and Society, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - SFA - Sexual Freedom Associates (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Shamrock Distributors (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Shaz Press Inc. (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Robert Sherwood (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Show Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - S.I.I. (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Mr. Sir. (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Synergistic Mail Corp. (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Social Research Corp. (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Soldyrelse (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Space Trac (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Spartan Book and Film Club (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Specialty Items Co. (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Spectra (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Stardak Publishing Co., Inc. (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Stevens Agency (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - S.P. Stober (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Sovereign Advertising, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Jim Stryker (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Studio "9" (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Studio Bookshop (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Skyward Productions (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Studio Press (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Studio Services (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Sunshine Beach Club (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Swednafilm Internationale (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Tangents; Target (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - T.A.P. (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Telstar Productions (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Temple Rialto (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Terry Sanders (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Therapeutic Products Co. (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Timely Books (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Tom Kelley (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Toro (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Tropic Book Service (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - T.R.T. (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Tru-Art (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Alan Tuck Assoc. (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Ultima Sales Co. (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Turnabout Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - U.N.C.L.E. (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - United Surgical Distrs. (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Universal Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Universal Sales (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Universal Specialties (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - University Press (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Vagabond Club (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Venture Books (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Vigor and Vitality Books (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Viking Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Visual Enterprises (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Visual Information and Education (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Waterfront Books (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Westrep Associates (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - West Studios (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Williamshouse Associates (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Wingate and Bevins (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Wishbone Productions, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - XXX (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Zephyr Publications, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 130)